所到之处一片残骸
annihilating everything in their path.
我们还收到消息  下元大道也被毁
We're also getting reports of destruction on Shimomoto Boulevard.
我觉得大家还是不要去那里为好
I think it would be smart for your to avoid that area.
这场机器人肆虐的背后黑手是谁
Who is behind this robo-rampage?
-糟了  -山哥干的
- Oh, no. - Yama.
-他非法制造了大白  -是大白们
- He bootlegged Baymax? - Baymaxes.
复数  很多
Plural. So plural.
好吧  现在有一群杀手机器人在城里
Okay, so, a bunch of killer robots are loose in the city.
-知道这听起来像什么吗  -一个我做过的噩梦
- Know what this sounds like? - A nightmare I had once?
不  是我们超能陆战队大展身手的好机会
No! It sounds like a job for Big Hero 6!
根据记者的意见...
In this reporter's opinion...
你们看到T恤后肯定会喜欢这个名字
You guys are gonna love the name when you see the T-shirts.
警察可以处理
The police can handle this.
我们处理不了了
We can't handle this!
机器人肆虐